my-search.com 2013-10-30

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated: November 5, 2010

International Web Services, LLC ("Licensor", "we" or "us") is the licensor of this plugin (the "Plugin"). Licensor knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy is a binding part of Licensor's License and Terms of Use, which is available web.archive.org/terms (together with this Privacy Policy, the "Agreement") and explains the type of information Licensor collects through its website and browser companion software ("Plugin Service") and what Licensor does with it. If you download and use Licensor's Plugin Service software or use Licensor's website (the "Site"), you will be bound by the terms of the Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time so you should check it frequently.

Licensor may collect certain information about your web usage and sites you have visited, which may be shared with third parties and used for advertising. NOTE: THE PLUGIN COLLECTS AND STORES INFORMATION FOR LICENSOR ABOUT THE WEB PAGES YOU VISIT AND YOUR ACTIVITY ON THOSE PAGES, SUCH AS IMPRESSIONS AND CLICKS. IN SOME CASES, INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE PLUGIN SERVICE MAY BE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE, AND IN SOME CASES INFORMATION (INCLUDING INFORMATION FROM OR ABOUT PAGES OF SOCIAL MEDIA WEBSITES YOU VISIT) MAY BE USED OR SHARED WITH THIRD PARTIES FOR PURPOSES OF DISPLAYING TARGETED ADVERTISEMENTS TO YOU. BUT PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US, AND WE DO NOT ATTEMPT TO ANALYZE WEB USAGE DATA TO DETERMINE THE INDIVIDUAL IDENTITY OF ANY PLUGIN USER.

**What Information About Users Does Licensor Gather?**

Here are the types of information we gather.

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on the Site or give us in any other way. You provide most such information when you use the Site or the Plugin Service. For instance, if you register for an account with us, we may collect your name, email address, country of origin, and, if you choose, your nickname, telephone number, website, company, and title. If you download and install the Plugin Service software, which provides our Plugin, we collect any information voluntarily provided by you during the installation and registration process, which can include demographic information such as gender, age, occupation, household income, zip code and country. Demographic information may be correlated to web usage information collected during your use of the Plugin Service. In addition, you might provide us with personal identifying information, such as mobile telephone number, when you communicate with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise, or complete a questionnaire, subscription form or a contest entry form. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing and improving our services, delivering targeted content and advertisements that may be of interest to you, and communicating with you.

  * **Automatic Information We Collect From the Plugin Service:** When you use the Plugin Service, we may collect information about the websites you visit and the advertisements that you see on those websites, the searches you perform using search engines, the ways in which you use various Plugin Service features (including whether the Plugin Service is still installed on your computer), and the pages you view (especially social media pages). For example, the Plugin Service may collect information about page views, impressions and clicks, as well as similar web usage information. For every webpage you view while using the Plugin Service, the Plugin Service software transmits and stores information associated with your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which may include a domain name, the full URL of the webpage you are visiting, general information about your browser; general information about your computer's operating system; your Licensor cookie number or other identifying alphanumerical information enabling Licensor to identify your computer; and the date and time the above information is logged. All of this above information may be logged together in a single data string for each webpage you visit. Each string is logged in our database in the chronological order received from our users. In addition, the Plugin Services may collect information about what cookies are stored on your computer, which enables Licensor to determine which websites you have visited in the past.Although this information may contain some personal identifying information, Licensor does not use it to determine the identity of individual users or correlate it to your email address or other personal identifying information that you give us or our affiliates, except as required by subpoenas, court orders, investigations or other legal requirements. When you download the Plugin Service software, and at times during your use of the Site and/or Plugin Service, we may transmit Licensor cookies to the hard drive of your computer. The Plugin Service also automatically collects information about the online advertisements that are displayed on the websites you visit - specifically, the text, source, and URL of the online ad - and the terms you choose when you use search engines to search the Web. Licensor also may periodically collect usage statistics from Plugin Service users that describe the frequency of use of each Plugin Service feature.Finally, to ensure accurate information about the number of Plugin Service users and to check for updates to the Plugin Service, the Plugin Service periodically sends a signal to Licensor containing basic information such as the IP address of your computer.

  * **Automatic Information We Collect from the Site:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Site. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the Site, when you use the Plugin Service, or when you view advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Licensor on other Web sites.Examples of the information we may collect and analyze when you use our website include the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from the Site, including date and time; cookie; web pages you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call us. During some visits to the Site we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

**What About Cookies?**

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser, and through our Plugin Service, to enable our systems to recognize your browser.

  * The Help portion of the Plugin on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

**How Do We Share the Information and Use the Information We Receive?**

_Automatic Information and Aggregated Information_ : We may share (1) automatic information we collect from the Plugin Service or the Site, including IP address and your web usage data as described above, and (2) aggregated information (i.e., information about you and other users collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you) with third parties and affiliated companies to develop and deliver targeted advertising through the Plugin Service, on our websites and on websites of third parties. Some of these advertisements may be displayed to you within existing webpages you are viewing.In addition, information from social media sites you visit may be used by us and our advertising partners to display targeted advertisements to you. You hereby consent to these practices, as well as to the other disclosures and uses of your information described in this Privacy Policy. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our websites or users of the Plugin Service and the most popular features or services accessed. This information may be used to develop content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising. Automatic and aggregated information may also be shared with the same types of third parties and for the same purposes as personal identifying information, as described below.

_Personal Identifying Information_ : We may share user data with our parent, affiliate and subsidiary companies to provide you with information about a variety of products and services that might interest you. These companies will comply with this Privacy Policy and applicable privacy and security laws and, at a minimum, in any commercial e-mail they send to you, will give you the opportunity to choose not to receive such e-mail messages from that company in the future. Except for personal identifying information which may be automatically collected with non-personal web usage information as an incidental effect of the operation of the Plugin Service and not to identify you as an individual (see above), personal identifying information may be shared with unaffiliated third parties only as described below.

  * **Providers of Bundled Software or Services:** We may offer search or other services that are powered or provided by another company. You can tell when a third party is involved in a given service offering, and, if you choose to use the service, we will share information related to your use of the service with that company. For example, the Plugin may be bundled with, or require the installation of, third-party software, such as search engine Plugins, and in such event, we may transmit your search term and IP address to the third-party provider so that it can provide you with the requested search results. Such bundling enables the Plugin to perform the functions requested by you and to collect information as described in our Privacy Policy. Also, if you download our Plugin Service from a third party website, the Plugin Service may display the third party's brand, and consequently that third party may receive information about your use of the Plugin Service. You should be aware that information may be collected and stored directly by the providers of such third-party software and services and that your use of such software or services (including use in connection with our Plugin) is governed by the terms of use and privacy and security policies and practices of the applicable third-party providers and not by this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the terms of use and privacy and security policies of all third-party Plugins and other software or services that may be bundled with the Plugin or installed in connection with the Plugin.

  * **Third-Party Service Providers:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include storing and analyzing data, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), hosting, and providing customer service. These third-party service providers have access to user information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the user consents otherwise). Also, in the event that Licensor or substantially all of our assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, user information will be one of the transferred assets.

  * **Protection of Licensor and Others:** We release account and other user information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our License and Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Licensor, our users, or others.

  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when personally identifiable information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

In general, we may use information (whether personal identifying information or not) that we collect about you to:

  * deliver the products and services that you have requested;
  * send you offers that you have opted in to receive;
  * manage your relationship with us and provide you with customer support;
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or third parties;
  * develop and display content and advertising (such as targeted ads) tailored to your interests on our websites and other websites;
  * verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with promotions, contests and sweepstakes;
  * enforce our Agreement;
  * protect Licensor, our Plugin Service, our websites, our customers and/or our other users from fraud, hacking or other harm;
  * cooperate with legal, criminal or regulatory investigations or proceedings;
  * manage our business; and
  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of information collection.

**How secure Is Information About Me?**

  * Licensor uses commercially reasonable computer security safeguards to protect its databases and servers against risks of loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification, or inadvertent or improper disclosure of data.
  * Only authorized employees and authorized third-party service providers are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions.

  * If you have an account with us, it is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**What About Third-Party Advertising and Links to Other Websites?**

We work with third-party websites, advertisers, and Internet advertising companies working on their behalf (collectively, "Ad Companies"). These Ad Companies may send (or "serve") advertisements directly to your browser, from our Site, our Plugin Service, and from other websites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. The information practices of these Ad Companies are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

**What Choices Do I Have?**

  * Licensor does not require that you provide us with personal identifying information in order to use most of our services. Therefore, you can always choose not to provide such information.
  * To learn how to uninstall the Plugin and any bundled software, please visit <http://www.dropinsavings.com/uninstall>
  * If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, contact us to modify your preferences.
  * The Help portion of the Plugin on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.
  * The Plugin Service enables you to update certain browser configuration settings, such as your home page or your default search provider.  If supported, you may configure these options during the installation process and in the Options menu in the Plugin Service.

**Plugin Service Provided from the United States**

If you are downloading or using the Plugin Service software from outside the United States, please be aware that your information (including information collected through the Plugin Service) will be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By downloading the Plugin Service software and using the Plugin Service, which are provided exclusively from the United States, you hereby consent to the transfer of your information to the United States and its collection, storage, sharing and use as described in this Privacy Policy.You further agree that all transactions relating to the Plugin or Plugin Service shall be deemed to have occurred in the United States.

**Are Children Allowed to Use Licensor?**

Licensor does not offer products or services for use by children. If you are under 18, you may not use the Site or the Plugin Service.Licensor does not knowingly collect information from children.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Licensor may change any of the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy, at any time in its sole discretion. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL BE POSTED ON THIS WEBSITE HERE WHEN THEY BECOME EFFECTIVE. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR REVIEWING THE NOTICE AND ANY APPLICABLE CHANGES. When we post changes to this PRIVACY POLICY, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this PRIVACY POLICY.Accordingly, you should periodically check the"last updated" date at the top of THIS Privacy Policy, so that you can familiarize yourself with any changes.

YOU AGREE THAT YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE PLUGIN SERVICE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND AFTER THE CHANGES TAKE EFFECT WILL CONSTITUTE YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGES. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO FUTURE CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, STOP USING THE PLUGIN SERVICE AFTER THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF SUCH CHANGES AND UNINSTALL THE PLUGIN.
